[
    {
      "id": 1,
      "topic": "Basic security concepts",
      "question": "A small program that gets installed on a computer while browsing the Internet. The basic function of active content is to provide an interactive Internet experience through videos and toolbars. Sometimes, active content is used to gain unauthorized access to a computer, and then damage the data stored on it or install malicious software on it.",
      "answers": ["Active content", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "topic": "Basic security concepts",
      "question": "C.I.A.",
      "answers": ["Confidentiality, Integrity, Availability", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "topic": "Basic security concepts",
      "question": "The process of reconverting the encrypted data into a readable and usable form",
      "answers": ["Decryption", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "topic": "Basic security concepts",
      "question": "The process of converting data into an unreadable and unusable form. Encryption is done to prevent unauthorized access of data, especially during data transmission over the Internet",
      "answers": ["Encryption", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "topic": "Basic security concepts",
      "question": "Information that describes how a message is encrypted",
      "answers": ["Key", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "topic": "Basic security concepts",
      "question": "A unique string of characters that a user types in as an identification code. It is a security measure used to restrict access to computer systems and sensitive files",
      "answers": ["Password", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "topic": "Basic security concepts",
      "question": "The name by which a user is identified to a computer system or network. To access a computer protected by username and password, a user needs to enter the correct combination of username and password",
      "answers": ["User name", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "topic": 0,
      "question": "A filter that blocks unreliable and unauthorized information from the Internet before it reaches your computer or a private network. It provides additional protection against threats such as hackers and viruses. A firewall also helps to ensure computer privacy by restricting external access by any unauthorized user",
      "answers": ["Firewall", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "topic": "Basic security concepts",
      "question": "A person who uses computer expertise to gain unauthorized access to a computer, and then misuses or tampers the programs and data stored on the computer",
      "answers": ["Hacker", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "topic": "Basic security concepts",
      "question": "A company that provides Internet connectivity to individuals, businesses, and organizations",
      "answers": ["ISP", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "topic": "Principles of secure design",
      "question": "Keeping a userâ€™s data, including personal files and e-mail messages, such that the data is not accessible by anyone without appropriate permission",
      "answers": ["Computer privacy", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "topic": "Principles of secure design",
      "question": "An Internet security protocol that ensures secure data communication by encrypting the information transmitted",
      "answers": ["SSL", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "topic": "Principles of secure design",
      "question": "Prevents access to data from a server or a network by sending more requests than a server can handle",
      "answers": ["Denial of Service (DoS) attacks", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "topic": "Principles of secure design",
      "question": "Two or more computers attack a server at the same time, with the attacking computer infected with malware that instructs the computer to continually send requests to the server",
      "answers": ["Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS)", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "topic": "Principles of secure design",
      "question": "Method of which to prevent physical access to a computer",
      "answers": ["Physical security", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "topic": "Principles of secure design",
      "question": "The act or instance of making a duplicate copy of a program, a disk, or data",
      "answers": ["Backup", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "topic": "Principles of secure design",
      "question": "A method of preventing access to the server by using an intermediary server to direct traffic away from the main server",
      "answers": ["Proxy server", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "topic": "Web basics",
      "question": "Temporary memory on your computer that is sometimes used to store local copies of files opened when you browse the Internet",
      "answers": ["Cache", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "topic": "Web basics",
      "question": "A small file on a computer that is created when a user visits a Web site",
      "answers": ["Cookie", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "topic": "Web basics",
      "question": "The act of extracting personal information, such as passwords and credit card details, from computer users and then using the information for malicious purposes",
      "answers": ["Phishing", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "topic": "Web basics",
      "question": "A computer program that is installed on your computer without your knowledge. Spyware can secretly send out information about your Web browsing habits or other personal details to another computer through the network",
      "answers": ["Spyware", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "topic": "Web basics",
      "question": "A check that asks the user to confirm whether or not they wish to go ahead with an instruction",
      "answers": ["Verification", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "topic": "Web basics",
      "question": "A computer program that is designed to cause malfunctioning of a computer or damage the data stored on the computer",
      "answers": ["Virus", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "topic": "Web basics",
      "question": "A computer program that propagates itself across computers, usually by creating copies of itself in each computer's memory",
      "answers": ["Worm", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "topic": "Web basics",
      "question": "Software that is intended to disrupt or modify a computer system and its data without the user's knowledge",
      "answers": ["Malware", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "topic": "Web basics",
      "question": "Using emails to capture data by tricking a user to visit a fake website, and thus tricks the user into entering personal data",
      "answers": ["Pharming", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "topic": "Web basics",
      "question": "A communication which asks for data to be transferred",
      "answers": ["Request", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "topic": "Web basics",
      "question": "Security which prevents access to a computer even if the user has physical access",
      "answers": ["Authentication", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "topic": "Other",
      "question": "A method of protecting the rights of an originator of a creative work, such as text, piece of music, painting, or computer program, through law",
      "answers": ["Copyright", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "topic": "Other",
      "question": "Any information available on the Internet is an intellectual property, which is legally owned by the person who created it. The owner of an intellectual property has the exclusive rights to control the use of this information",
      "answers": ["Intellectual property", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 31,
      "topic": "Other",
      "question": "Verbal defamation. This is a punishable offense",
      "answers": ["Slander", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 32,
      "topic": "Other",
      "question": "A sudden increase in line voltage, which may lead to the damage of electronic devices, such as computers",
      "answers": ["Power surge", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 33,
      "topic": "Other",
      "question": "An individual who develops contact with Internet users, through chat rooms, online forums, or e-mail, to exploit them financially or involve them in dangerous relationships",
      "answers": ["Online predator", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 34,
      "topic": "Other",
      "question": "Unauthorized copying of copyrighted software without obtaining the license or permission of its copyright owner",
      "answers": ["Software", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 35,
      "topic": "Other",
      "question": "An irrelevant and unsolicited e-mail message sent by an unknown sender",
      "answers": ["Spam", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 36,
      "topic": "Other",
      "question": "The use of physical characteristics such as fingerprints, voice patterns, and face shapes as means of identification",
      "answers": ["Biometrics", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 37,
      "topic": "Other",
      "question": "A program which finds and removes viruses from a computer by scanning it",
      "answers": ["Antivirus ", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 38,
      "topic": "Other",
      "question": "",
      "answers": ["", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    },
    {
      "id": 39,
      "topic": "Other",
      "question": "",
      "answers": ["", "wrong1", "wrong2", "wrong3"]
    }
   ]